In this video, I will show you how to make a twist panel as shown in the video.
Today, let's make a twist panel as shown in the video.
First, let's use the plus point line tool to score.
This is a reference for the position of the seam allowance.
Then, we switch to the edit panel tool and use the internal line tool.
In the position we need to add, add an internal line of 1 to 8 mm.
Note that if you need to cancel the extension of the internal line here, you will create an internal line in parallel.
This internal line will be our reference line for adding the seam allowance.
Next, we add the internal circle on the end point of the corresponding internal line.
Set the diameter to 10 mm and then click OK.
Then this circle is the position of the twist panel that we want to fix.
Now let's copy it and paste it out.
Click on the position that needs to be pasted and click OK.
You can see that there are several points that need to be pasted.
Next, let's separate the points on the internal circle.
This is convenient for the next process.
Because we only need a semi-circular fixed panel line here, so we delete the other half.
OK, so now we have a semi-circular.
Next, we use the twist tool to add the extension at the center point of the corresponding circle.
Then switch to the select move twist tool.
First copy the first twist, then right-click on the appropriate position and paste the twist to the position below.
It is the same, right-click on the position that needs to be pasted, you can add multiple extension twists.
Then we need to set the twist layer.
Harden the panels in the middle.
Make them a little closer to the middle.
You can also make the two-layer panels flatter.
Then turn off the simulation.
Next, set the layer of sewing here.
I have two layers here.
You can also make the two-layer panels flatter.
Then turn off the simulation.
Next, we use the twist tool to add the extension.
The width is set to 30 mm.
Then the height is set to 1 mm.
We switch to the add point division tool.
First add a point to the edge to make it easier to locate.
Then right-click on the position at the bottom edge.
Switch to the length division.
In the middle, separate a section of 8 mm in length.
Set the direction as the center.
Then this section, go with our half-circle position.
Go to the center to make a seam.
The two ends of the panel line are fixed to the other side.
Pay attention to the direction of the seam on both ends.
The middle can be separated a little bit.
After the seam is finished,
we choose this panel line.
Press the 3D window key.
Move it to the seam position.
Rotate the view.
Pull it out a little bit.
Remember to modify the particle diameter of the panel.
Freeze the panel in the back.
After adjusting the particle diameter, simulate.
Adjust it a little bit.
Apply the corresponding fabric to it.
Based on the fabric to be applied to the panel line,
copy a new fabric.
Then change it to a relatively hard physical attribute.
You can see the effect of the panel line after simulation.
Then copy the remaining panel line.
Here, repeat the operation of the first panel line.
Go to the panel line on both sides and sew it.
Then do the same.
Also fix the position of the panel line.
Then untie the two panels.
Select all the buttons.
Then turn off the conflict.
Simulate.
Select the panel line.
Change the particle diameter to 3.
Correct the Global
Then change the bundle thickness to 1.
Turn on the panel line.
Then gently pull the toggle
And use the button even to proposing this gotcha HTML function.
Open both of the couplings again.
Again simulate again.
Similar.
Then we unseal the panel.
Add an adhesive strip to the position close to the back
Then set it as a 5-way stretch
Then this twist is finished here